Guide to the American Dance Festival Photographic Materials Collection, circa 1930-2008
American Dance Festival Archives
American Dance Festival Photographic Materials collection circa 1930-2008
American Dance Festival Archives Box 90772 Durham, North Carolina, 27708-0772 USA Phone: 919-684-6402 Fax: 919-684-5459 Email: adfarchives@americandancefestival.org
American Dance Festival
19.4 linear feet
The American Dance Festival is a non-profit organization committed to serving the needs of dance, dancers, choreographers, and professionals in dance-related fields. It presents a six and a half week summer festival of modern dance performances and educational programs, hosts community outreach activities, and sponsors numerous projects in the humanities. Its mission is to create and present new dance works, preserve the modern dance heritage, build wider national and international audiences and enhance public understanding and appreciation for modern dance, and provide training and education for dancers and choreographers. The collection includes photographic materials created and collected by the American Dance Festival, including negatives, contact sheets, prints, and transparencies.
ADF.002
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Patrons must sign the Acknowledgement of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights form before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The American Dance Festival Photographic Materials Collection was received by the American Dance Festival Archives as transfers and gifts.
Historical Note
The American Dance Festival is a non-profit organization committed to serving the needs of dance, dancers, choreographers, and professionals in dance-related fields. It presents a six and a half week summer festival of modern dance performances and educational programs, hosts community outreach activities, and sponsors numerous projects in the humanities. Its mission is to create and present new dance works, preserve the modern dance heritage, build wider national and international audiences and enhance public understanding and appreciation for modern dance, and provide training and education for dancers and choreographers.
Collection Overview
The collection includes photographic materials created and collected by the American Dance Festival, including negatives, contact sheets, prints, and transparencies.
Collection Arrangement
Materials are arranged in five series:
Company and Biographical
Bennington College
Connecticut College
Duke University
Unidentified
The Company and Biographical series contains images of choreographers, performing companies, ADF faculty members, ADF staff, and other individuals. The Bennington College series contains images of the campus, faculty, staff, classes, and showings from the Bennington School of Dance from the early 1930s until 1942. The Connecticut College series contains images of campus, faculty, staff, classes, showings, and other events occurring at the American Dance Festival during its tenure at Connecticut College, which ended in 1977. The Duke University series contains images of campus, faculty, staff, classes, showings, and other events associated with the American Dance Festival during its time at Duke University. The Unidentified series contains images that have yet to be identified or dated.
Subject Headings
American Dance Festival; Bennington School of the Dance; Connecticut College American Dance Festival; Choreographers -- United States; Modern dance -- United States; Photographs
Contents of Collection
- Company and Biographical, circa 1930-2008
  The Company and Biographical series contains images of choreographers, performing companies, ADF faculty members, ADF staff, and other individuals.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - 5 by 2 Dance Company, 1973, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Adams, Carolyn (Faculty), 1997, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Adams, Carolyn, 1997-1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - ADF Repertory Company, Asparagus Beach (Rudy Perez), 1972, (prints) (Box 1)
  - ADF Repertory Company, El Penitente (Martha Graham), 1972 (6 folders), (prints) (Box 1)
  - ADF Repertory Company, Emperor Jones (Jose Limon), 1972, (prints) (Box 1)
  - ADF Repertory Company, Flickers (Charles Weidman), 1972, (prints) (Box 1)
  - ADF Repertory Company, New Dance (Doris Humphrey), 1972, (prints) (Box 1)
  - ADF Repertory Company, undated, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - ADF Repertory Company, With My Red Fires (Doris Humphrey), 1972, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Ae Sook Chang, 1992, undated, (prints) (Box 1)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 1985-1987, (prints) (Box 1)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 1986-1987, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 25)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 1987-1988, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 1997, 1999, 2002, (prints) (Box 1)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - African American Dance Ensemble, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Ahn, Sungsoo (YCC), 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Ahuju, Savitri, 1966-1967, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Ailey, Alvin, 1987, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Ailey, Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 1960, (8 x 10 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negatives) (Box 25)
  - Ailey, Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 1960, 1962, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Ailey, Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 1972, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Ailey, Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 1972, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Ailey, Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, circa 1980, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Ailey, Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Ailey, Alvin Ailey Repertory Ensemble, 1997, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Alba, Maria, undated, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Albert, Arnold, Tanzania, 1985, (prints) (Box 1)
  - American Ballroom Theater, undated, 1986, (prints) (Box 1)
  - American Dance Machine, 1978, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - American Repertory Dance Company, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - American Repertory Dance Company, 1996,1998, 1999, 2002, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Angiel, Brenda, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Angiel, Brenda, 1998-1999, 2002, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Angiel, Brenda Angiel Dance Company, 1999, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Anthony, Mary, undated, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Jack (Faculty), 1997, undated, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Jack, 1993-1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Art of Black Dance and Music, 1983, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Atsugi, Bonjin Atsuji Dance Company, 1982, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Aulmomonto, 1992, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Aulmomonto, 1992, (35 mm slide) (Box 25)
  - Aviles, Nelson, 1990, (prints) (Box 1)
  - Baek Cho Kim, 1960, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Baganova, Tatiana (ICCP), 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Baganova, Tatiana (ICCP), 1999, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Baganova, Tatiana (ICCP), 2001, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bagouet, Dominique, 1983, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Balasaraswati, 1977, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Balasaraswati, undated, (4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 25)
  - Bales, Bill, 1967, (2 1/4 b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Bales, William, 1961, 1966, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bali, Margarita, Argentina, 1985, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Ballard, Orville, 1964, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Ballet Contemporaneo del Teatro Municipal General San Martin, 1989, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Ballet Contemporaneo del Teatro Municipal San Martin, 1989, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 25)
  - Ballet du Lac Tumba, 1991, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Ballet Espanol, Ximenes-Vargas, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Ballet Mechanique, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Ballet Philippines, 1984, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Ballet Philippines, 1984, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Ballet Philippines, 1984, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Ballet Russes, 1995, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Ballet Theatre de L'Arche, 1983, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bamonte, Karen, 1988, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Batson, Glenna, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Bausch, Pina, 1999, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bausch, Pina, undated, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Baytos, Betsy, 1980, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Beadle, David, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Beatty, Talley, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Beatty, Talley, Teaching, Publicity, circa 1950, 1988, 1993, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Beatty, Talley, undated, (printer's negatives from 1993 Scripps Award) (Box OS1)
  - Beatty, Talley, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 25)
  - Beatty, Talley with Others, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Beavers, Wendell (Faculty), 1996, 1998, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Beavers, Wendell, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Beck, Jill (Faculty), 1993-1994, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bellini, Juan Carlos, 1963, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bendongue, Fred, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Bendongue, Fred, 2000, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Benitez, Maria, 1983, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Benitez, Maria Benitez Estampa Flamenca, 1983, (35 mm slide) (Box 25)
  - Benitez, Maria Benitez Spanish Dance Company, 1983, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Benoniova, Marcella, 1985, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Berg, Harriet, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bergsohn, Isa, 1978-1979, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Berland, Erika, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Berry, Stafford, 2002, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bettis, Valerie, 1949, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bhaskar and His Orchestra, 1967, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bird, Bonnie, 1974, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bogart, Tracy, 1998, (36 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Boyce, Johanna (Emerging Generations), 1981, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Boyce, Johanna Boyce and Performance Group, 1982, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Brechenmacher, Bernard, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Brezer, Laz, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Brodie, Keith, circa 1993, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bromberg, Ellen, 1989, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Buster, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Ronald K., 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Ronald K., 1993, 1997, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Ronald K., 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Ronald K., 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Ronald K., 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Ronald K./EVIDENCE, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Ronald K./EVIDENCE, 1995, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Ronald K./EVIDENCE, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Ronald K./EVIDENCE, 2001, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha, 1990-1997, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Trisha, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Trisha, 2000, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company, 1984, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company, 1984, undated, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company, 1989, 1993, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company, 1990, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company, 1997, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company, 2000, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Dance Company, 2000, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Company (with Dave Douglas), 2000, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Dance Company, 2002, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Trisha Brown Dance Company, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Brumachon, Claude, 1989, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Brumachon, Claude, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Buirge, Susan Buirge Project, 1983-1985, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Bullock, Jeffery, 1998, 2000, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Bullock, Jeffery, 2000, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Buntz, Gina, 1983, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Burchfield, Donna Faye, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Burchfield, Donna Faye, 1997, 2000, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Butler, Ethel, 1940, 1995, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Byrd, Bonnie, 1964, (35 mm slides) (Box 25)
  - Byrd, Donald, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Byrd, Donald, 1994, 1997, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Byrd, Donald Byrd/The Group, 1997, (prints) (Box 2)
  - Byrd, Donald Byrd/The Group, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 25)
  - Cage, John (with Merce Cunningham), 1966, 1983, 1985, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Calabash Dance Company, 1981, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cardona, Wally, 1996, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cardona, Wally, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Carlson, Ann, 1990, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Carlson, Ann, 2000, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Carlson, Ann, 2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Carlson, Ann Carlson and Company, circa 1988, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Carr, Deborah Carr Theatre Dance Ensemble, 1985, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Carr, Deborah Carr Theatre, 1985, (35 mm slide) (Box 26)
  - Carroll, Vinette, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Carter, Cornelius, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Carter, Cornelius, 1996, 1997, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Chang, Mabel Dai Chee, 1995, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Chang, Mabel Dai Chee, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Childs, Lucinda, undated, (4 x 5 b&w negatives) (Box 26)
  - Chow, Pewan (ICR), 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Chow, Pewan, 1994, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Christopher, Patricia, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Chryst, Gary, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Clark, Nathan, 1995, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1980, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 26)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1980, 1995, 1999, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1985, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1985, 1993, 1995, 1999, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1995, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1995, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Clarke, Martha, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Clarke, Nathan, 1998, (35 mm slide) (Box 26)
  - Cloud Gate Dance Theater, 2002, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cloud Gate Dance Theatre, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Clouser, James and Sonya Zarek (Faculty), 1971, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cobb, Catlin, 1983, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cohen, Ze'eva, 1975, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Comfort, Jane, 1998, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Comfort, Jane Comfort and Company, 2000, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Comfort, Jane Comfort and Company, 2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Compagnie de Dance L'Equisse, Performance, 1983, 1987, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Compagnie de Dance L'Equisse, Publicity, 1987, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Conetic Dance Theater, 1974, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Contradanza, 1985-1989, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Contradanza, 1989, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 26)
  - Cratty, Bill (Faculty), 1988, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Crowsnest, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Crowsnest, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cummings, Blondell, Chicken Sou, circa 1983, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, James Cunningham and Dancers, 1970, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce, 1979-1985, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce, 1985, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Cunningham, Merce, 1997, undated, (2 1/4 contact sheets, 35 mm contact sheet, 35 mm copy slide) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce, Looking at Dance, 1996, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce, Looking at Dance, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce, Panel Discussions, 1984, 1996, 1998, 2001, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce, Publicity, 1973, 1981-1986, 1995, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce, Teaching and Performing, 1957, 1961, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1959, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1976-1980, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1978-1979, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1981, 1984, 1988-1989, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1981-1983, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1982-1988, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1984, (2 1/4 b&w negatives, 8 x 10 b&w negatives, 4 x 5 b&w negatives) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1984-1985, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1987-1989, 1991, 1997, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1991-1992, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1993, 1996, 1998, 2001, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1996-1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, circa 1967, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Merce Cunningham Dance Company, undated, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Curran, Sean, 1997, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Curran, Sean, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Currier, Ruth, 1958, 1961, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Currier, Ruth, 1964, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Currier, Ruth, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Curtis-Smith, Curtis, undated, (prints) (Box 3)
  - Dabin, Joel (Faculty), undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dadura, Erika, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dahrendorf, Sabine (ICR), 2001, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dai Rakuda Kan, 1982, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dai Rakuda Kan, 1982, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Dai Rakuda Kan, 1987, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dairakudakan, 1986, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Dalby, Norma, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Danat Danza, 1992, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dance Advance, undated, (2 1/4 b&w negatives) (Box 26)
  - Dance Concoctions, 1973, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dance Hawaii (includes pre-1900 hula dancer photos), 1987, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dance Hawaii, 1984, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Dance Hawaii, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 26)
  - Dance Indonesia, 1984, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Dance Indonesia, 1984, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dance Kumikokimoto, 1985, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1977, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dancers from Bali, 1979, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Danzahoy, 1982, 1988-1989, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Danzahoy, circa 1989, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Darsow, Fred (YCC), 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 26)
  - Darsow, Fred, 1993, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Davis, Chuck, 1979-1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Davis, Chuck, 1984, 1986, undated, (35 mm slides, b&x contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Davis, Chuck, 1984, 1999, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Davis, Chuck, 1999, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Davis, Chuck, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Davis, Chuck Davis Dance Company, 1974, 1982, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Davis, Linda, 1994-1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 26)
  - Davis, Lynda (Faculty), 1993, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Davis, Rosalind, Community Outreach, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 26)
  - Day, Ruth, 1992, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1988, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1988, 1990-1992, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1990-1991, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1993, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1994-1996, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1995-1996, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 1998, 2002, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, ADF On Tour, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, undated, (prints) (Box 4)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, undated, (35 mm slides, 8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 27)
  - de Jong, Betty, 1958, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - de Lavallade, Carmen, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - de Lavallade, Carmen, 2001, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dean, Laura, 1978-1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Dean, Laura, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dean, Laura, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dean, Laura Dean and Dance Company, 1974, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dean, Laura Dean and Dance Company, 1979, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dean, Laura Dean Dancers and Musicians, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Dean, Laura Dean Dancers and Musicians, 1982, 1986-1987, 1990, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Dean, Laura Dean Dancers and Musicians, 1985-1986, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dean, Laura Dean Dancers and Musicians, 1987, 1989, 1993, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Deboo, Astad, 1984, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - del Valle, Guido, 1960, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dendy, Mark, 1981, 1986, 1994, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dendy, Mark, 1992-1994, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dendy, Mark, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dendy, Mark, 2000, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dendy Dance, 1992, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dendy, Mark Dance and Performance, 1994, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Dendy, Mark Dendy Dance and Performance, 1994, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dendy, Mark Dendy Dance and Theatre, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dendy, Mark Dendy Dance and Theatre, 1996, 2000, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dendy, Mark Dendy Dance and Theatre, 2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dendy, Mark Dendy Dance and Theatre, Publicity, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Denishawn, undated, (4 x 5 b&w negative, 5 x 7 b&w negative) (Box 27)
  - Desca, Eva, 1949, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Desrosiers Dance Theatre 1985, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Destine, (Jean-)Leon 1963, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Detroit All-City High School Dance Group, 1956, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Diachenleo, Nada, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dietz, Margaret, 1954, (prints) (Box 5)
  - DiMuro, Peter, 1999, (prints) (Box 5)